festivalsherpa.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Festival Sherpa | Online Guide to Festivals

We, ARA Infotech Pvt. Ltd. **,** a private limited company (hereinafter referred to as **“Company”** ), having its registered office at **206 – Konark Shram, 156 Tardeo Road, Mumbai – 400034, India** , the creator of this Privacy Policy ensure our firm commitment to your privacy vis-à-vis the protection of your priceless information. In order to endow You with Our uninterrupted use of services, We may collect and, in some circumstances, disclose information about You. To enhance better protection of Your privacy We provide this notice explaining Our information practices and the choices You can make about the way your information is collected and used.

_All visitors to Our website are advised to read and understand Our Privacy Policy carefully, as by accessing the Website You agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy and consent to the collection, storage and use of information relating to You as provided herein._

_If You do not agree with the terms and conditions of Our Privacy Policy, including in relation to the manner of collection or use of Your information, please do not use or access the Site._

If You have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, You should contact our customer support desk at [thesherp@festivalsherpa.com](mailto:thesherp@festivalsherpa.com)

ANY CAPITALIZED WORDS USED HENCEFORTH SHALL HAVE THE MEANING ACCORDED TO THEM UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. FURTHER, ALL HEADING USED HEREIN ARE ONLY FOR THE PURPOSE OF ARRANGING THE VARIOUS PROVISIONS OF THE AGREEMENT IN ANY MANNER. NEITHER THE USER NOR THE CREATERS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY MAY USE THE HEADING TO INTERPRET THE PROVISIONS CONTAINED WITHIN IT IN ANY MANNER.

**1.  DEFINITIONS**

a. “We”, “Our”, and “Us” shall mean and refer to the creators of this privacy policy.

b. “You”, “Your”, “Yourself” and “User” shall mean and refer to natural and legal individuals who use the Website.

c. “Website” shall mean and refer to [festivalsherpa.com](https://www.festivalsherpa.com/) owned and operated by the Company.

d. “Personal Information” shall mean and refer to any personally identifiable information that We may collect from You. For removal of any doubts, please refer to Clause 2.

e. “Third Parties” refer to any Website, company or individual apart from the User and the creator of the Website.

**2\. OVERVIEW**

We commit to respecting Your online privacy data. We further recognize Your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“ **Personal Information** “) You share with us. Information that is considered personal about You by Us includes, but is not limited to, Your name, age, address, email address, phone number, your travel documents, visa, passport or any other contact information. This privacy policy also applies to data We collect from users who are not registered as members of this site, including, but not limited to, browsing behaviour, pages viewed etc.

**3\. NOTIFICATION OF MODIFICATIONS AND CHANGES TO THE T &C AND PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to change the Terms and Privacy Policy from time to time as We deem fit, without any intimation to You, and Your continued use of the Website will signify Your acceptance of any amendment to these terms. You are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy on a regular basis. Should it be that You do not accept any of the modifications or amendments to the Terms, You may terminate Your use of this Website immediately.

**4\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Our Application’s online requisition form requires Users to give Us contact information (like your name, address, telephone number and email address). As a registered member You are required to provide a valid email address at registration and choose a username or alias that represents your identity on our Application. You may however, visit out site anonymously.

**5\. COOKIES**

We use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of our Applications. “Cookies” are files sited on your hard drive containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website/application. When you visit the website/application again, the cookie allows that website/application to recognize your browser. We offer certain features that are only available through the use of a “cookie”. We use Cookies to identify individual user buying pattern, overall demographics buying patter in order to help us to improve your user experience and the overall quality of our services. Cookies can also help us provide information, which is targeted to your interests.

**6\. EXTERNAL LINKS ON APPLICATION**

The Website may include hyperlinks to other web Applications or content or resources. We have no control over any Website or resources, which are provided by companies or persons other than us. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for the availability of any such external Website or resources, and do not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such Website or resources.

**7\. OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

You acknowledge and agree that we are not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external websites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such Websites or resources. These third-party service providers and Third-Party Websites may have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your personal information that you may be subject to. We recommend that when you enter a Third-Party Website, you review the Third Party Website’s privacy policy as it relates to safeguarding your personal information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Application. Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

a. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

b. To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

c. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

d. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

e. To send periodic email.

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. We may release your personal information to a third-party in order comply with a Court Order or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Our Terms of Use. We may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with our Copyright Policy as mentioned in the Terms of Use as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, we may disclose name, address, country, phone number, email address and company name.

**8\. CONFIDENTIALITY**

You further acknowledge that the Website may contain information which is designated confidential by us and that you shall not disclose such information without our prior written consent.

Your information is regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities.

We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by us will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.

**9\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Applications. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications would always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

**_a. External Service Providers_** _:_ There may be a number of services offered by external service providers that help you use our Services. If you choose to use these optional services, and in the course of doing so, disclose information to the external service providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their private policy.

**_b. Other Corporate Entities:_** We share much of our data, including personally identifiable information about You, with our parent and/or subsidiaries that are committed to serving your online needs and related services, throughout the world. Such data will be shared for the sole purpose of enhancing your browsing experience. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other members. It is possible that We and/or its subsidiaries, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that we would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent it occurs).

**c. _Law and Order_** _:_ We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.

**10\. THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**11.  CHILDRENS’ ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), our policy is located at **Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.** We do not disclose or share our demographics data with anyone or any third party advertiser.

**12\. ACCESSING, REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PROFILE**

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted except your display name, during registration. If you change any information we may keep track of your old information. You can change your registration information such as: name, address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, and profile.

We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored ‘back up’ systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

**13\. CONTROL OF YOUR PASWORD**

When you sign up to become a Member, you will also be asked to choose a password. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. It is important that you protect it against unauthorized access of your account and information by choosing your password carefully, and keeping your password and computer secure by signing out after using our services.

You agree not to use the account, username, email address or password of another Member at any time or to disclose your password to any third party. If you choose to share this information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password and therefore should review each third party’s privacy policy. You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. You agree to notify us immediately if you suspect any consistent unauthorized use of your account or access to your password even after changing it.

**14\. OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our Website or on other Website throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

**15\. SECURITY**

We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. We do not recommend transfer of sensitive information and bank account details via the Website. Users are recommended to do so offline, on the phone or via personal emails. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet. You therefore agree that any security breaches beyond the control of our standard security procedures are at your sole risk and discretion.

**16\. DISCLAIMER**

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information (including sensitive information bank account number) will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will always remain private. As a user of the Website, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Application, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Application.

**17\. CONTACTING US**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [thesherp@festivalsherpa.com](mailto:thesherp@festivalsherpa.com).
